I get questions all the time about some
我总是会对某些问题提出疑问
of the new concepts in machine learning
机器学习中的新概念
and what they really mean so for example
例如他们真正的意思
I get asked what is one hot encoding and
我被问到什么是热门编码和
why should I use it it does seem very
为什么我应该使用它看起来非常
inefficient you know that's a great
效率低下你知道这很棒
question so let's take a look at the
问题所以让我们来看看
answer by digging into some code will
通过挖掘一些代码来回答
also see how a function called Arg max
还可以看一个名为Arg max的函数
complements this perfectly and saves you
完美补充并拯救你
a lot of coding here's the popular iris
这里有很多编码是流行的虹膜
classification data set where the values
分类数据集的值
implemented in a JavaScript array you'll
你可以在JavaScript数组中实现
notice that there are five values in
请注意，有五个值
each entry four of which are features of
每个条目中有四个是特征
the iris and the fifth which will be
虹膜和第五个将是
zero one or two
零一两
is the classification the classes are
是类的分类
shown here with iris setosa being zero
这里显示iris setosa为零
iris versicolor being one an iris
iris versicolor是一个虹膜
virginica being two now this seems to be
维吉尼亚现在似乎是两个
a really efficient encoding but when
一个真正有效的编码，但何时
doing machine learning you often have to
做机器学习你经常需要
transform this into something that
将此转化为某种东西
appears to be less efficient such as one
似乎效率较低，如一个
hot encoding which you can see here and
热门编码，你可以在这里看到
instead of 0 1 & 2 for the values you
而不是0 1
have an array with 3 values in it and
有一个数组，其中包含3个值
here we've only got three options of
在这里，我们只有三种选择
flower if we had more options this array
如果我们有这个阵列的更多选项花
would be much bigger the index of the
将指数大得多
array is set to 1 for the relative
对于相对数组，数组设置为1
flower so for example for its Atossa
因此，例如它的阿托萨花
the first element is 1 and everything
第一个元素是1和一切
else is 0 and for virginica the third
else为0，而virginica为第三
element is 1 and everything else is 0
element为1，其他所有为0
now this might seem a little strange but
现在这看起来有点奇怪但是
when you consider the neural network
当你考虑神经网络
that's doing the classification they're
他们正在进行分类
designed with the number of output nodes
设计有输出节点的数量
equal to the number of classes that you
等于你的班级数
want to determine we're picking between
我想确定我们之间的选择
three classes here so I have three
这里有三个班，所以我有三个班
output nodes these three output nodes
输出节点这三个输出节点
will then produce three probabilities
然后将产生三个概率
the probability that you match class 0
你匹配0级的概率
the probability match class 1 or the
概率匹配等级1或
probability in match class 2 so it might
匹配等级2中的概率可能
look something like this
看起来像这样
so now when training the network we can
所以现在我们可以训练网络
train it from matching values ie if the
从匹配值训练它，即如果
flowers of classes who we want to train
我们想要训练的班级花
it with a 0 desired output from neuron 0
它与神经元0的0期望输出
0 desired output from neuron
来自神经元的0期望输出
and a one desired output from neuron two
和神经元2的一个所需输出
so that's one hard encoding it may not
所以这可能不是一个硬编码
look efficient from a storage
从存储看起来高效
perspective but it Maps really neatly to
透视，但它真的很巧妙地映射到
our desired output and thus is very
我们想要的输出因此是非常的
efficient for training another function
有效地培养另一种功能
called Arg max is then really handy for
之所以称为Arg max则非常方便
helping you find the desired values so
帮助您找到所需的值
instead of searching through a list to
而不是通过列表搜索
find the biggest value it would
找到最大的价值
transform that list of priorities into
将优先级列表转换为
something like this and from there you
像这样的东西，从那里你
can derive the correct class so let's
可以得到正确的类，所以让我们
jump back into the code and we'll see
跳回代码，我们会看到
this in action
这在行动中
here I'm going to evaluate a flower with
在这里，我要评估一朵花
the features five point eight two point
功能五点八点两点
seven five point one and one point nine
七点五分一点九
I know that this is an iris virginica
我知道这是一个虹膜维吉尼亚
which is class two but let's see what
这是第二类，但让我们看看是什么
the neural network gives me well first
神经网络首先给了我很好的
take a look at the raw prediction and
看看原始预测和
then we'll take a look at the prediction
然后我们来看看预测
that's been determined using Arg max
这是使用Arg max确定的
let's run this in the browser when i
我在浏览器中运行它
refresh the JavaScript will start
刷新JavaScript将启动
executing and here you can see my epochs
执行，在这里你可以看到我的时代
and my loss at that epoch it's steadily
我在那个时代的失败是稳步的
decreasing which is good and now I get
减少这是好的，现在我得到
my classification and you can see that
我的分类，你可以看到
has very low probabilities for 0 and 1
0和1的概率非常低
and a very high probability for 2 which
并且2的概率非常高
is what we'd expect if I then execute
如果我再执行，那就是我们所期望的
Arg max on this I will get to consider
Arg max对此我会考虑
the amount of code that you would have
您将拥有的代码量
to write in this case it's not a lot
写这个案子并不是很多
with just two classes but if there are a
只有两个班，但如果有一个
lot more classes
更多的课程
and you needed to find the biggest you'd
你需要找到最大的你
have a lot of coding to do but Arg max
有很多编码要做，但Arg max
does this for you given that these
鉴于这些，为你做这件事
values are in a tensor I hope this was a
价值是张量我希望这是一个
useful explanation of one heart encoding
一个心脏编码的有用解释
and how it complements an Arg max
以及它如何补充Arg max
function these are some of the concepts
功能这些是一些概念
that are a bit different when you're
你有点不同
coding for machine learning but they're
编码机器学习，但他们是
incredibly useful and powerful
非常有用和强大
one harden coding is great because it's
一个硬化编码很棒，因为它是
a way of mapping your classes to the
一种将类映射到的方法
shape that a neural network outputs
神经网络输出的形状
values an Arg max is a function that
值Arg max是一个函数
saves you writing a lot of code to go
为您节省了大量代码
over all those values to find the
在所有这些价值观找到
biggest there's lots of useful functions
最大的有很多有用的功能
and transforms like these intensive flow
并像这些密集的流动一样转变
and we'll continue to cover them on this
我们将继续在此报道
channel so go ahead and hit that
频道所以继续前进并击中它
subscribe button now thank you
订阅按钮现在谢谢
[Music]
[音乐]